<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cilo</string>
    <string name="your_guide_to_a_low_carbon_lifestyle">Your guide to a low-carbon lifestyle</string>
    <string name="join_with_your_company">Join With Your Company</string>
    <string name="join_as_an_individual">Join As An Individual</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="please_sign_in_to_continue">Please sign in to continue</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="by_selecting_sign_up_below">By selecting \'sign up\' below, I agree to the&#160;</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="company_code">Company code</string>
    <string name="where_did_you_hear_about_cilo">Where did you hear about Cilo?</string>
    <string name="company_code_with_code">Company code: %s</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="dont_have_an_account_yet">Don\'t have an account yet?</string>
    <string name="to_join_as_individual_or_sign_in">to join as individual or sign in</string>
    <string name="to_join_with_company_or_sign_in">to join with company or sign in</string>
    <string name="set_your_carbon_budget">Set Your Carbon Budget</string>
    <string name="add_your_first_purchase">Add Your First Purchase</string>
    <string name="check_out_leaderboards">Check Out Leaderboards</string>
    <string name="what_is_a_cilo">What is a Cilo?</string>
    <string name="lets_get_started">Let\'s get started!</string>
    <string name="items">Items</string>
    <string name="cilos_per_kg">Cilos / kg</string>
    <string name="add_items_to_purchase">Add Items To Purchase</string>
    <string name="search_items">Search items</string>
    <string name="type">Type</string>
    <string name="size">Size</string>
    <string name="origin">Origin</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="item_cilo_value">₵%1$s / kg</string>
    <string name="kg">kg</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="select_type">Select Type</string>
    <string name="new_retailer">New Retailer</string>
    <string name="something_missing">Something Missing?</string>
    <string name="quantity">Quantity</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="retailer">Retailer</string>
    <string name="search_retailers">Search Retailers</string>
    <string name="confirm_changes">Confirm Changes</string>
    <string name="new_">New</string>
    <string name="save_purchase">Save Purchase</string>
    <string name="summary">Summary</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="percent_of_weekly_budget">%.2f%% of weekly budget</string>
    <string name="spent_this_week">spent this week</string>
    <string name="set_budget_to_get_started">Set budget to get started!</string>
    <string name="set_new_carbon_budget">Set New Carbon Budget</string>
    <string name="cilos_per_week_budget_text">"₵%d / week - %s"</string>
    <string name="five_ton_lifestyle">5 Ton Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="well_on_your_way">Well On Your Way</string>
    <string name="a_great_start">A Great Start</string>
    <string name="better_than_average">Better Than Average</string>
    <string name="for_the_most_serious">For the most serious climate warriors</string>
    <string name="giving_the_flexatarian_lifestyle">Giving the flexatarian lifestyle a crack? Try this budget to keep you on track</string>
    <string name="you_eat_a_lot_of_meat">You eat a lot of meat but you\'re trying to cut down</string>
    <string name="stick_to_this_budget">Stick to this budget and you\'ll be doing better than the average UK citizen</string>
    <string name="x_cilos_left">%s Cilos left</string>
    <string name="x_cilos_over">%s Cilos over</string>
    <string name="for_x_days">for %s days</string>
    <string name="cilo">Cilo</string>
    <string name="and_finally">And finally…</string>
    <string name="how_should_i_track_my_carbon_footprint">How should I track my carbon footprint?</string>
    <string name="what_do_the_tiers_mean">What do the tiers mean?</string>
    <string name="where_does_the_data_come_from">Where does the data come from?</string>
    <string name="should_i_offset_my_emissions">Should I offset my emissions</string>
    <string name="invite_friends">Invite friends</string>
    <string name="get_in_touch">Get in touch</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="your_profile">Your profile</string>
    <string name="all_employees">All employees</string>
    <string name="teams">Teams</string>
    <string name="admins">Admins</string>
    <string name="total_spent">₵%s spent</string>
    <string name="all_time">All time</string>
    <string name="week_beginning">Week beginning</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="charts">Charts</string>
    <string name="leaderboards">Leaderboards</string>
    <string name="reduce">Reduce</string>
    <string name="add_number_of_people">Add number of people</string>
    <string name="how_many_people_split">How many people should these items be split between, including yourself? (Must be a whole number)</string>
    <string name="split_items">Split Items</string>
    <string name="this_cannot_be_undone">This cannot be undone. You will lose all the data you\'ve recorded into the app.</string>
    <string name="set_target_points">Set Target - %s Points</string>


    <string name="cilos_are_the_currency">Cilos are the currency this app uses to measure your carbon spending. When you spend 1 Cilo (₵1) on a product, it means for that product to be made, transported, stored and disposed of, greenhouse gases equivalent to 1kg of carbon dioxide had to be emitted into the atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="in_other_words">In other words, a cilo is equivalent to a kilogram of carbon dioxide emissions - a carbon kilo if you will! (That\'s why it\'s pronounced with a hard "C", like "kilo")</string>
    <string name="in_scientific_papers">In scientific papers, “kgCO2e” is the unit that is typically shown to measure something’s carbon footprint, but it’s the same thing.</string>
    <string name="so_why_give_it_a_new_name">So why give it a new name? Everything we buy has a carbon cost, as well as a financial one, and it’s important that we as individuals have the option to monitor our carbon spending in the same way we monitor our financial spending.</string>
    <string name="with_that_we_would_be_able_to_find">With that, we’d be able to find ways, specific to us, to reduce our carbon footprint in ways that have the biggest impact for the least effort.</string>
    <string name="we_would_be_able_to_set_ourselves">We’d be able to set ourselves carbon budgets to help keep our carbon spending in check.</string>
    <string name="we_would_be_able_to_indentify_things">We’d be able to identify the things we buy that have the biggest carbon cost, and start thinking of those things as expensive treats which we could slowly but steadily reduce our consumption of.</string>
    <string name="we_would_be_able_to_choose_to_buy">And, eventually, we’d be able to choose to buy from businesses whose products have a lower carbon cost than their competitors. That would not only have the benefit of helping us reduce our own carbon footprint, but also of creating climate competition between businesses, and therefore encouraging those businesses to make genuine, verifiable improvements in their supply chains to reduce the carbon footprint of their products.</string>

    <string name="there_are_three_main_benefits">There are three main benefits of having an understanding of the carbon footprint of things you buy:</string>
    <string name="benefit_one">1.) It helps you reduce your individual climate impact.</string>
    <string name="benefit_two">2.) It encourages businesses to reduce the carbon footprint of their products.</string>
    <string name="benefit_three">3.) If we make the effort to understand our environmental impact and take action to reduce it, it will make it much harder for governments and people in power to avoid doing the same.</string>
    <string name="reducing_our_individual_climate_impact">1.) REDUCING OUR INDIVIDUAL CLIMATE IMPACT:</string>
    <string name="it_may_seem_an_obvious_thing">It may seem an obvious thing to say, but unless we understand our carbon footprint, it’s going to be very hard to reduce it.</string>
    <string name="its_been_almost_impossible">Unfortunately though, it’s been almost impossible up to now for us as individuals to develop an understanding of how to reduce our climate impact beyond the generic advice such as “try and minimise flying”, “cut down on meat and dairy”, and “lower the heating”.</string>
    <string name="that_is_all_very_good_advice">To be clear, that is all very good advice. But imagine you were saving up for something. Maybe you want to get married, so you need to be a bit frugal for a year or two to save up for the wedding.</string>
    <string name="all_that_information_you_had_about">Now imagine that all the information you had about how to save money was that flying, beef, and heating are all very bad… and that’s about it. When you went to the shop nothing had a price tag on it and when you bought something at checkout you had no idea what you’d just spent.</string>
    <string name="it_would_be_tough_right">It would be tough right? You’d probably have to think about trimming the invite list.</string>
    <string name="thats_essentially_what_weve_been">That’s essentially what we’ve been contending with when it comes to reducing our climate impact as individuals.</string>
    <string name="tracking_your_carbon_footprint">Tracking your carbon footprint with Cilo will allow you to figure out exactly where your biggest carbon outlays are coming from. And you can then find ways to reduce your carbon spending that are the least effort for you.</string>
    <string name="so_if_your_biggest_carbon_spending">So if your biggest carbon spending is on things you’d be happy to consume less of then you could try and slowly but steadily reduce how much of it you buy.</string>
    <string name="but_if_its_a_product_or_service">But if it’s a product or service that you can’t live without then maybe you can try and find a company that sells it which is genuinely and verifiably making the effort to reduce the environmental impact of its products.</string>
    <string name="if_youre_tracking_your_carbon_footprint">If you’re tracking your carbon footprint you’ll be able to set yourself realistic goals and hopefully over time you’ll see your footprint come down.</string>
    <string name="if_were_going_to_tackle_climate_change">If we’re going to tackle climate change it’s much better to continually make small improvements that we can sustain than to make big unrealistic targets that we quickly give up on. Having a true understanding of the numbers makes it much easier to do that.</string>
    <string name="some_people_will_argue_that_any_carbon">Some people will argue that any carbon reductions we make as individuals are so small compared to total global emissions that it’s not worth doing. But it’s important to remember that we are a society of individuals.</string>
    <string name="the_impact_of_one_person">The impact of one person reducing their carbon footprint by 10% is small, but the impact of 20%, 50%, or 100% of us reducing our footprint by 10% would be absolutely massive, while also being very achievable.</string>
    <string name="incentivse_business_to_reduce">2.) INCENTIVISE BUSINESSES TO REDUCE THEIR CARBON FOOTPRINT:</string>
    <string name="at_the_moment_it_seems_that_just">At the moment it seems that just about every company, even those that are literally digging up the fossil fuels from the ground, is claiming that it is having a positive impact on climate change and is good for the planet generally.</string>
    <string name="the_issue_is_that_its_hard">The issue is that it’s very hard for us as consumers to figure out which of them are telling the truth. Again, this comes from not having enough information. Companies don’t tell us what the carbon footprint of their products are, and even if they did, we wouldn’t know if it was better than average for that type of product.</string>
    <string name="if_we_knew_all_that">And even if we knew all that, if we didn’t know what our total carbon footprint was, we wouldn’t be able to put the saving into context.</string>
    <string name="track_our_carbon_footprint_though">If we track our carbon footprint though, this can all change. Businesses that claim their products are low carbon can get this verified scientifically by an independent source. Consumers would then be able to see the genuine carbon savings they could make by buying such a product, and decide if it’s worth any extra cost that might be associated.</string>
    <string name="businesses_will_be_able_to_compete">Businesses will be able to compete as to who can provide the most low carbon product, driving a new race to the bottom line, only this time that line is zero emissions.</string>
    <string name="demonstrate_to_governments_that_were">3.) DEMONSTRATE TO GOVERNMENTS THAT WE\'RE WILLING TO TAKE ACTION:</string>
    <string name="it_is_governments_that_have_the_most_power">It is governments that have the most power to have an impact in slowing and eventually halting climate change, but they have continually proven over the last 50 years that they will not do so under their own volition.</string>
    <string name="a_huge_reason_for_that_is_because">A huge reason for that is because they are afraid that we will refuse to elect them in the future if they pursue policies that make our lives in any way more difficult than they were before.</string>
    <string name="if_we_demonstrate_that_we_are_willing">If we demonstrate that we are willing to take action it will make it much more difficult for governments to use that as an excuse for their lack of it.</string>
    <string name="one_vote_every_four_or_five_years">One vote every four or five years isn’t enough. Protests and marches haven’t had the desired effect. We need to keep doing both of these, but we also need to put our carbon where our mouth is and start changing things ourselves.</string>

    <string name="although_the_carbon_footprint">Although the carbon footprint of food is often portrayed as meat = bad, dairy = quite bad, and the rest = good, things are unsurprisingly a little more complicated than this. The tiers are there to give you a quick understanding of where on the spectrum of good to Amazon-rainforest-cleared-beef-bad different products lie.</string>
    <string name="tier_one_products_have">Tier one products have the lowest carbon footprint and it is mostly made up of locally produced, seasonal fruit and vegetables, while tier six is at the other end of the spectrum, with the most commonly bought products in this category being beef, lamb, prawns and hard cheese.</string>
    <string name="the_larger_the_contribution">The larger the contribution of tier 1 and tier 2 products to your overall footprint, the better.</string>
    <string name="the_footprint_range_for_each_tier">The footprint range for each tier is as follows:</string>
    <string name="tier_one_cilos">Tier 1: &lt; 1 Cilo/kg</string>
    <string name="tier_two_cilos">Tier 2: 1 – 2 Cilos/kg</string>
    <string name="tier_three_cilos">Tier 3: 2 – 4 Cilos/kg</string>
    <string name="tier_four_cilos">Tier 4: 4 – 8 Cilos/kg</string>
    <string name="tier_five_cilos">Tier 5: 8 – 16 Cilos/kg</string>
    <string name="tier_six_cilos">Tier 6: &gt; 16 Cilos/kg</string>

    <string name="the_footprint_database">The footprint database was put together by doing a meta-analysis of existing life cycle assessment studies and articles.</string>
    <string name="for_products_for_which_no_direct_data">For products for which no direct data could be found, we looked at their supply chains and what went into making them and made assumptions based on that to calculate a footprint estimate.</string>
    <string name="the_data_in_its_current_form">The data in its current form is far from perfect. Some estimates will be too high and others too low. But we are confident that where we have put things on the spectrum of “good” to “bad” (ie, what tier an item is in) is broadly correct.</string>
    <string name="we_are_even_more_confident_that_after">And we are even more confident that after a month of tracking, whichever products the app tells you are the ones that are contributing the most to your total footprint will be correct.</string>
    <string name="we_know_that_the_data_is_the_most_important">With that being said, we know that the data is the most important thing for Cilo to get right. We want to provide data that is more accurate, more specific, and more understandable than anyone else.</string>
    <string name="that_is_why_as_cilo_grows">That is why as Cilo grows, the amount of time and investment it puts into improving the database will grow proportionally.</string>
    <string name="calculating_and_estimating_carbon_footprints">Calculating and estimating carbon footprints is a very complicated process and no matter how good our methods get it will always be possible to improve them. But just because something can’t be perfected doesn’t mean it can’t still be very useful.</string>
    <string name="if_you_have_a_background_in_life_cycle_assessment">If you have a background in life cycle assessment and you think there’s something that could be improved in the database we’d love to hear from you! We are always trying to get better.</string>

    <string name="in_order_to_keep_global_warming">In order to keep global warming below 1.5°C many governments and organisations are setting targets to achieve “net zero” emissions by 2050. What this means is that any emissions they are still making by then will need to be offset by removing at least an equal amount of greenhouse gases from the atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="despite_the_fact_that_an_awareness">Despite the fact that an awareness of the need for offsets has existed for decades, no technology or methodology has ever been developed that would allow us to extract greenhouse gases from the atmosphere on a large scale. And as yet, none are close.</string>
    <string name="the_issue_with_net_zero_targets">The issue with net zero targets is that they can give companies and governments an excuse to keep emitting as they always have done while saying their "net" emissions will reduce over time because a new technology will come along which allows them to offset them. It is important to know that no such silver bullet technology exists.</string>
    <string name="it_will_be_far_easier_and_cheaper">It will be far easier and cheaper for us as a society to reduce our emissions than to offset them. Some level of offsetting will be necessary because there are technologies which will be very hard to decarbonise, such as flying, and that is why continuing to develop offsetting technology is hugely important work.</string>
    <string name="but_we_have_to_have_two_separate">But we have to have two separate targets as a society, one for reducing our emissions and one for offsetting them, so as to keep governments and companies honest. Otherwise, as happened recently, you will get oil companies promoting their oil as carbon neutral!</string>
    <string name="most_studies_predict_that_the_easiest_path">Most studies predict that the easiest path to net zero by 2050 would be to reduce emissions by 90% and offset the remaining 10%.</string>
    <string name="many_footprinting_tools_give_individuals">Many footprinting tools give individuals a vague notion of their footprint and then ask them to pay to offset them. We think this is more of a money grab than a helpful solution to climate change. It’s part of the reason we created Cilo.</string>
    <string name="its_also_important_to_know_that_if">It’s also important to know that if a company is claiming to offset your emissions by, for example, funding a renewable energy project, developing more efficient household goods, or protecting land against deforestation, while these can be very important and worthy projects to support when done right, they don’t actually lead to negative emissions - no extra CO2 is extracted from the atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="so_the_emissions_that_your_actions">So the emissions that your actions produced remain there. As such it’s better to think of them as charitable donations rather than true offsets.</string>
    <string name="cilo_as_a_company_is_focussing">Cilo as a company is focusing on reducing emissions, not offsetting them.</string>
    <string name="whether_you_decide_to_offset">Whether you decide to offset your emissions is of course entirely up to you. If you do decide to do so, our recommendation would be, firstly, not to worry about the unavoidable emissions (we all need to eat!), and then for the avoidable ones if you truly want to offset them follow the Berners-Lee Rule, which is as follows:</string>
    <string name="to_stand_a_hope_of_a_legitimate_offset">“To stand a hope of a legitimate offset claim, you need to show that the carbon you remove is genuinely additional to everything that needed to happen anyway without your avoidable impact.</string>
    <string name="this_rules_out_all_the_finite_nature_based_solutions">“This rules out all the finite nature based solutions (tree-planting, soil sequestration) that humanity already needs to maximise and takes us into unproven technologies costing at present hundreds of dollars per tonne.”</string>

    <string name="we_at_cilo_believe_individuals">We at Cilo believe individuals can play a huge role in the fight against climate change, and we wanted to create a tool that would make it easier for anyone to take action.</string>
    <string name="our_aim_is_to_help">Our aim is to help as many people have as big an impact as possible.</string>
    <string name="if_you_have_any_thoughts">If you have any thoughts on how we can do this better, issues with the app, questions, or you just want to reach out then please do. We\'d love to hear from you!</string>
    <string name="saved">saved</string>
    <string name="points">points</string>
    <string name="targets">Targets</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="first_purchase_recorded">First purchase recorded! Next…</string>
    <string name="great_work_next">Great work! Next…</string>
    <string name="set_target">Set Target</string>
    <string name="why_is_this_beneficial">Why is this beneficial?</string>
    <string name="previous_purchases">Previous purchases</string>
    <string name="cilo_community">CILO COMMUNITY</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="create_retailer">Create Retailer</string>
    <string name="join_your_work_group">Join your work group</string>
    <string name="edit_items">Edit Items</string>
    <string name="split_selected_items">Split Selected Items</string>
    <string name="edit_target">Edit Target</string>
    <string name="delete_target">Delete Target</string>
    <string name="new_target">New Target</string>
    <string name="reduce_by">Reduce by</string>
    <string name="target_duration">Target duration</string>
    <string name="target_saving">Target saving</string>
    <string name="save_changes">Save changes</string>
    <string name="potential_saving">(potential saving)</string>
    <string name="update_target">Update Target</string>
    <string name="delete_selected_items">Delete Selected Items</string>
    <string name="its_time_to_set_your_targets">It\'s time to set your targets for the year ahead!</string>
    <string name="youll_earn_1_point_for_every">You\'ll earn 1 point for every ₵1 saved</string>
    <string name="you_can_set_as_many_targets">You can set as many targets as you like, but you\'ll only earn points on the three with the highest saving</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="forgot">FORGOT</string>
    <string name="account_details">Account Details</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="log_out">Logout</string>
    <string name="employees">Employees</string>
    <string name="team">Team</string>
    <string name="not_right_now">Not right now</string>
    <string name="create_profile">Create Profile</string>
    <string name="create_your_profile">Create your profile</string>
    <string name="add_a_username">Add a username below to create your profile</string>
    <string name="input_the_code">Input the code provided by one of your company\'s Cilo champions.</string>
    <string name="or_if_youd_like_to_nominate">Or if you\'d like to see your company join the Cilo movement, nominate them below.</string>
    <string name="enter_code">Enter code</string>
    <string name="join_company">Join Company</string>
    <string name="nominate_company">Nominate Company</string>
    <string name="earn_points_by_adding_purchases">Earn points by adding purchases, creating targets, referring the app to friends, and more!</string>
    <string name="points_leaderboard">Points Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="let_s_say_this_tip_was_to">Let\'s say this tip was to switch from cow\'s milk to oat milk. You might only want to do this half the time, in which case you\'d choose 50%. But if you wanted to cut out cow\'s milk entirely, you\'d choose 100%</string>
    <string name="select_team">Select Team</string>
    <string name="select_all">Select All</string>
    <string name="deselect_all">Deselect All</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="cilos_are_the_currency_dialog_text">Cilos are the currency this app uses to measure your carbon spending.</string>
    <string name="cilo_is_the_equivalent_of">1 Cilo (₵1) is the equivalent of 1kg of carbon dioxide emissions.</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset Password?</string>
    <string name="if_you_forgotten_your_password">If you\'ve forgotten your password we can email you a link to reset it. Please note you\'ll need to click this link on your mobile device.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="send_reset_link">Send reset link</string>
    <string name="search_employees">Search employees</string>
    <string name="search_teams">Search teams</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="please_choose_your_team_office_and_username">Please choose your team, office and username</string>
    <string name="successfully_joined_company_profile">Successfully joined %1$s\'s profile</string>
    <string name="failed_to_join_company_profile">Could not join company profile, continue without joining?</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong_joining_company">Something went wrong when attempting to join the company, you can continue and try to join the company again from the settings page</string>
    <string name="log_out_question">Log Out?</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete">Confirm delete</string>
    <string name="search_admins">Search admins</string>

</resources>